[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Donald, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Donald", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Hello, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Hello", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "What do you make of the basic substance of this debate, which is whether Mitt Romney's record at Bain Capital was predominantly a good one or a bad one?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "basic", "substance", "of", "this", "debate", ",", "which", "is", "whether", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "record", "at", "Bain", "Capital", "was", "predominantly", "a", "good", "one", "or", "a", "bad", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, it wasn't a good one.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "a", "good", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bain Capital"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "But isn't one of the problems here, Donald, that people like you and Newt Gingrich who are now racing to support Mitt Romney over this battle have in the past attacked him for his record at Bain?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "n't", "one", "of", "the", "problems", "here", ",", "Donald", ",", "that", "people", "like", "you", "and", "Newt", "Gingrich", "who", "are", "now", "racing", "to", "support", "Mitt", "Romney", "over", "this", "battle", "have", "in", "the", "past", "attacked", "him", "for", "his", "record", "at", "Bain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I've been supporting him for a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "supporting", "him", "for", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bain"], "PERSON": ["Donald", "Newt Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$13", "$14 trillion", "$16 trillion"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "$", "CD", "CC", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "But is it the right battle ground for Mitt Romney, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "the", "right", "battle", "ground", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, first of all, we're not $13 or $14 trillion in debt, we're $16 trillion in debt and going up rapidly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "we", "'re", "not", "$", "13", "or", "$", "14", "trillion", "in", "debt", ",", "we", "'re", "$", "16", "trillion", "in", "debt", "and", "going", "up", "rapidly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cory Booker"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Do you think it's too vicious or do you think this is part and parcel of American political life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "too", "vicious", "or", "do", "you", "think", "this", "is", "part", "and", "parcel", "of", "American", "political", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, first of all, I know Cory Booker.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "know", "Cory", "Booker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ed Kline"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Now, are you saying that it would be fair game to go after President Obama based on his association with that man?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "are", "you", "saying", "that", "it", "would", "be", "fair", "game", "to", "go", "after", "President", "Obama", "based", "on", "his", "association", "with", "that", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, a book was just written by a great writer named Ed Kline.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "book", "was", "just", "written", "by", "a", "great", "writer", "named", "Ed", "Kline", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reverend Wright"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "But clearly if Reverend Wright comes into play and is deemed to be fair game, then wouldn't it be also fair game to go after Mitt Romney for his religion?", "question_tokens": ["But", "clearly", "if", "Reverend", "Wright", "comes", "into", "play", "and", "is", "deemed", "to", "be", "fair", "game", ",", "then", "would", "n't", "it", "be", "also", "fair", "game", "to", "go", "after", "Mitt", "Romney", "for", "his", "religion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I think the Democrats will use whatever they can use regardless of whether or not Reverend Wright is brought up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "Democrats", "will", "use", "whatever", "they", "can", "use", "regardless", "of", "whether", "or", "not", "Reverend", "Wright", "is", "brought", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wright", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Do you think it's a fairly silly way of attacking him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "fairly", "silly", "way", "of", "attacking", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "No, I think it's very cute, it's fun.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "cute", ",", "it", "'s", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What do you think of that argument?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, look.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "If Mitt Romney asked you what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Mitt", "Romney", "asked", "you", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "So many people have asked me that question lately.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "many", "people", "have", "asked", "me", "that", "question", "lately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Including saying yes to VP if he asked you?", "question_tokens": ["Including", "saying", "yes", "to", "VP", "if", "he", "asked", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, I don't think he's going to ask me, but certainly I have a very strong base of people that do like what I say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "ask", "me", ",", "but", "certainly", "I", "have", "a", "very", "strong", "base", "of", "people", "that", "do", "like", "what", "I", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Have you been asked to speak at the Republican convention this summer and if so will you say yes if you are?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "asked", "to", "speak", "at", "the", "Republican", "convention", "this", "summer", "and", "if", "so", "will", "you", "say", "yes", "if", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, a lot of people have been asking me whether or not I'd be interested in doing it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "have", "been", "asking", "me", "whether", "or", "not", "I", "'d", "be", "interested", "in", "doing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What have you got against Sacha Baron Cohen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "got", "against", "Sacha", "Baron", "Cohen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, I don't like, frankly, what he did to Ryan Seacrest.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "like", ",", "frankly", ",", "what", "he", "did", "to", "Ryan", "Seacrest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sacha Baron Cohen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "?", "question_tokens": ["?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Gregg, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Gregg", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I'm doing just fine.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "just", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Does it feel good to be alive?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "feel", "good", "to", "be", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Just great.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Is that how you feel?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "That's the way I feel.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "way", "I", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Or was it just to have fun making music?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "it", "just", "to", "have", "fun", "making", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Just to have fun making music.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "to", "have", "fun", "making", "music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Everything just came as a kind of accidental side effect of that love for music?", "question_tokens": ["Everything", "just", "came", "as", "a", "kind", "of", "accidental", "side", "effect", "of", "that", "love", "for", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "When you finished the book did you sit back and go, I wish I hadn't done that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "finished", "the", "book", "did", "you", "sit", "back", "and", "go", ",", "I", "wish", "I", "had", "n't", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Drugs.", "answer_tokens": ["Drugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You wish you never got involved with drugs?", "question_tokens": ["You", "wish", "you", "never", "got", "involved", "with", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Drugs and alcohol.", "answer_tokens": ["Drugs", "and", "alcohol", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "What did they do to you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "they", "do", "to", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "They make you crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "make", "you", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Do you still get as much fun from playing music as you always did?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "get", "as", "much", "fun", "from", "playing", "music", "as", "you", "always", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Is it the one constant in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "one", "constant", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "What does it do for you when it's just you and the music?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "do", "for", "you", "when", "it", "'s", "just", "you", "and", "the", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, I've gone on stage before three times with an abscessed tooth, and I got there and set down behind my ax and started playing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "gone", "on", "stage", "before", "three", "times", "with", "an", "abscessed", "tooth", ",", "and", "I", "got", "there", "and", "set", "down", "behind", "my", "ax", "and", "started", "playing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Don't even feel the pain of an abscessed tooth?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "even", "feel", "the", "pain", "of", "an", "abscessed", "tooth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Where does it say that?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "it", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "In your book.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Does it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "A scoop on your hands?", "question_tokens": ["A", "scoop", "on", "your", "hands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Does anybody else know this?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "anybody", "else", "know", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Two, three people.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", ",", "three", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How old is your fiance?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "is", "your", "fiance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "She is 24.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "is", "24", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "And how does she feel about becoming wife number seven?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "does", "she", "feel", "about", "becoming", "wife", "number", "seven", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "That's not what she's becoming.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "what", "she", "'s", "becoming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What made you take the plunge again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "take", "the", "plunge", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Well, because this time I am really in love.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "this", "time", "I", "am", "really", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Like you've never been before?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "you", "'ve", "never", "been", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "How many times do you think you've been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Those one sided, I think twice.", "answer_tokens": ["Those", "one", "sided", ",", "I", "think", "twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "You were only in love with two of your six wives?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "only", "in", "love", "with", "two", "of", "your", "six", "wives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "I'm assuming that was a compliment, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "assuming", "that", "was", "a", "compliment", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "That would be a scoop.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "a", "scoop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "You were in love with Cher, weren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "in", "love", "with", "Cher", ",", "were", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Cher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Have you said in touch with her?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "said", "in", "touch", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "From time to time, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "time", "to", "time", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Are you a good friend?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "good", "friend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Was that a hideous experience?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "a", "hideous", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "It was a hideous experience.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "hideous", "experience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Because the whole world wants a piece of you, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "the", "whole", "world", "wants", "a", "piece", "of", "you", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Oh, man.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "And how much of it was your fault that you kept having broken marriages, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "much", "of", "it", "was", "your", "fault", "that", "you", "kept", "having", "broken", "marriages", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "You got down on bended knee?", "question_tokens": ["You", "got", "down", "on", "bended", "knee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Do you remember your exact words?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "your", "exact", "words", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What is her name?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "her", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Shannon.", "answer_tokens": ["Shannon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "When are you getting married?", "question_tokens": ["When", "are", "you", "getting", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Do you think Shannon knows the real dude?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "Shannon", "knows", "the", "real", "dude", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shannon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Is that -- do you think that is a good thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "a", "good", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I think it's totally irrelevant.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "totally", "irrelevant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "You sing to her?", "question_tokens": ["You", "sing", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I would like to be remembered as a -- somebody who could rock your soul or make your cry with a song.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "as", "a", "--", "somebody", "who", "could", "rock", "your", "soul", "or", "make", "your", "cry", "with", "a", "song", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Atlantic"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "It just kept coming, didn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "just", "kept", "coming", ",", "did", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Yes, including on this side of the Atlantic impeaching a president.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "including", "on", "this", "side", "of", "the", "Atlantic", "impeaching", "a", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Or do you think the networks can still stay strong down the middle?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "think", "the", "networks", "can", "still", "stay", "strong", "down", "the", "middle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Well, I don't think it inevitably has to go into more partisanship.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "inevitably", "has", "to", "go", "into", "more", "partisanship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Is it -- is it extensively unhealthy to have partisan cable networks?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "extensively", "unhealthy", "to", "have", "partisan", "cable", "networks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "ESTIN: I think there's nothing wrong with opinion journalism.", "answer_tokens": ["ESTIN", ":", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "nothing", "wrong", "with", "opinion", "journalism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "You mean where news is presented in the opinionated manner?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "where", "news", "is", "presented", "in", "the", "opinionated", "manner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Did it become more fractious?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "become", "more", "fractious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Well, it changed fundamentally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "changed", "fundamentally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cory Booker", "Obama"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "you basically had it for the short term, doesn't he?", "question_tokens": ["you", "basically", "had", "it", "for", "the", "short", "term", ",", "does", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Yes, although my -- this is my personal opinion now, and I'm not responsible for covering these things, my reaction to the Cory Booker issue was he can support President Obama and not agree with him on every single thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "although", "my", "--", "this", "is", "my", "personal", "opinion", "now", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "responsible", "for", "covering", "these", "things", ",", "my", "reaction", "to", "the", "Cory", "Booker", "issue", "was", "he", "can", "support", "President", "Obama", "and", "not", "agree", "with", "him", "on", "every", "single", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter Jennings", "Bob Woodruff", "Dough Vogt"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "120522pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "And what was the lowest moment?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "the", "lowest", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Well, I mean, on a personal note, I mean, the death of Peter Jennings was a terrible moment and then the wounding of Bob Woodruff and his cameramen, Dough Vogt, in Iraq were awful.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "on", "a", "personal", "note", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "death", "of", "Peter", "Jennings", "was", "a", "terrible", "moment", "and", "then", "the", "wounding", "of", "Bob", "Woodruff", "and", "his", "cameramen", ",", "Dough", "Vogt", ",", "in", "Iraq", "were", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]